automanager.com 2014-06-30

# Legal Notices | AutoManager.com: Privacy Policy | AutoManager.com

* * *

Last Updated:  Nov 17, 2011

AutoManager is commited to protecting your privacy. You can visit most pages on our site without giving us any information about yourself, but sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, and this privacy statement explains data collection and use in those situations. This privacy statement applies to all of the products, services, and websites offered by AutoManager. Please read this complete privacy statement.

## Collection of your Personal Information

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are signing up to download a demo version of our software, downloading updates to our software, or requesting technical support or product information. Personal information collected by AutoManager often is limited to e-mail address, name, and phone number, but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested.

## How to Opt Out

If you no longer want to be contacted by AutoManager for any reason, click on the link below to enter your email address and phone number. Please allow up to 7 business days for us to remove you from our contact database.

  * Opt out of future communications from AutoManager

## Use of your Personal Information

We use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * To ensure our products are relevant to your needs.
  * To deliver services or software that you request or purchase.
  * To help us create and publish content most relevant to you.
  * To allow you access to limited entry areas of our site as appropriate.

In some limited-entry sections our website, we will use your personal information in order to provide you with personalized content. If you decline permission for this use of your information, you will not have access to those services.

We do not sell, rent, or lease our customer lists to third parties. We may work with other companies to provide limited services on our behalf that you have requested. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

AutoManager may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on AutoManager or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of AutoManager and its family of websites; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of AutoManager employees, users of AutoManager products or services, or members of the public.

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which AutoManager or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. AutoManager abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

## Control of your Personal Information

When you give us any personal information, AutoManager will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above.

AutoManager may send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical service or security issues related to a product or service you requested, or confirming you requested a product or service.

## Security of your Personal Information

AutoManager is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide in computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit sensitive information (such as a credit card number) over the internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

## Protection of Children's Personal Information

AutoManager.com is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children.

## Use of Cookies

AutoManager.com only requires cookies in connection with access to certain limited-entry sections of our website. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the AutoManager.com website, you will be able to view all of the general-access areas, however you will not be able to access some services on the site.

## Changes to this Policy

AutoManager will occasionally update this privacy policy. When we do, we will also revise the "Last Updated" date at the top of the privacy policy. For material changes to this policy, AutoManager will notify you by placing prominent notice on the website.
